「Alice good night」是这个吧！
等一下哦
让我看看！
谢谢推荐这首歌的人
n（拼音） 嘻嘻嘻
nu  ne  nuaaaaa——
啊 这是Deemo里面那首吧 是Deemo的
这就开始放了
*ne ne学语
*酝酿中
cho cho cho cho cho
啾  啾  啾  啾  啾
Maybe you will feel lost in your dreams
在这梦境中 也许你感到了失落空虚
Don't be scared
不要害怕
It's all right
微笑面对他
Alice good night
爱丽丝晚安
Good night
晚 安
Like the rabbits and the clocks all around
和你身边的兔子与时钟一同
Alice good night
爱丽丝晚安
Good night
晚 安
Let the sorrows just slowly fade away
就让悲伤渐渐散去
End this way
就在这条路的尽头
there must be a way
必将有新的未来
On the aimless ship passing away
会有一条小船带你漂离去未知的远方
Alice good night
爱丽丝晚安
Good night
晚 安
Just stay in the night
永远留在梦中吧
这会让人变困吧
We nevber travel in space hiding your secrets
我们的旅途从未能让你保存你的秘密
You always feel alone but
你总是觉得孤独 但是
it's ok to feel it
这也不会太可怕
Maybe we can feel dark after light
也许在光明过后我们会感到黑暗
don't be scared
不要害怕
I am here
我就在你身边
Alice good night
爱丽丝晚安
Good night
晚 安
Like the rabbits and the clocks all around
和你身边的兔子与时钟一同
Alice good night
爱丽丝晚安
Good night
晚 安
Let the sorrows just slowly fade away
就让悲伤渐渐散去
End this way
就在这条路的尽头
there must be a way
必将有新的未来
On the aimless ship passing away
会有一条小船带你漂离去未知的远方
Alice good night
爱丽丝晚安
Good night
晚安
Let's stay in the night
就让我们一同在这梦境中
让人变困了
真是首好曲子呢 是一首好曲子
真是好曲子
设置为我喜欢的曲子
OK!